Guide to the Charles and Shirley Weiss Collection of Opera Ephemera, 1951-2003 RL.11139
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Il Tabarro (Lyric Opera of Chicago, Chicago, IL), 1996 September 30 (Box 3)
- Il Tabarro (Spoleto Festival, Charleston, SC), 1999 May 28 (Box 3)
- Il Tabarro (New York City Opera, New York, NY), 2002 September 25 (Box 3)
- The Tale of Genji (Opera Theatre of St. Louis, St. Louis, MO), 2000 June 23 (Box 3)
- The Tale of Orpheus (Opera Theatre of St. Louis, St. Louis, MO), 1997 June 19 (Box 3)
- The Tales of Hoffmann (The Royal Opera, London, England), 1965 January 1 (Box 3)
- The Tales of Hoffmann (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1982 March 27 (Box 3)
- The Tales of Hoffmann (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1984 November 1 (Box 3)
- The Tales of Hoffmann (Opera Theatre of St. Louis, St. Louis, MO), 1986 June 22 (Box 3)
- The Tales of Hoffmann (Des Moines Metro Opera, Des Moines, IA), 1989 June 30 (Box 3)
- The Tales of Hoffmann (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1989 December 2 (Box 3)
- The Tales of Hoffmann (Spoleto Festival, Charleston, SC), 1991 May 25 (Box 3)
- The Tales of Hoffmann (The Washington Opera, Washington, DC), 1992 January 27 (Box 3)
- The Tales of Hoffmann (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1993 February 4 (Box 3)
- The Tales of Hoffmann (San Diego Opera, San Diego, CA), 1994 April 30 (Box 3)
- The Tales of Hoffmann (San Francisco Opera, San Francisco, CA), 1996 November 29 (Box 3)
- The Tales of Hoffmann (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1998 February 28 (Box 3)
- The Tales of Hoffmann (Houston Grand Opera, Houston, TX), 1998 November 1 (Box 3)
- The Tempest (The Santa Fe Opera, Santa Fe, NM), 1985 July 31 (Box 3)
- The Tempest (Des Moines Metro Opera, Des Moines, IA), 1986 July 11 (Box 3)
- The Tempest (The Dallas Opera, Dallas, TX), 1996 November 27 (Box 3)
- Thais (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1978 January 28 (Box 3)
- The Threepenny Opera (Triangle Opera Theater, Durham, NC), 1991 January 11 (Box 3)
- The Threepenny Opera (Playmakers Repertory Company, Chapel Hill, NC), 1998 April 15 (Box 3)
- Tickets, Please (Des Moines Metro Opera, Des Moines, IA), 1986 July 12 (Box 3)
- Tiefland (The Washington Opera, Washington, DC), 1995 March 28 (Box 3)
- Tosca (The Royal Opera, London, England), 1972 January 1 (Box 3)
- Tosca (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1979 January 6 (Box 3)
- Tosca (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1980 March 28 (Box 3)
- Tosca (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1985 March 11 (Box 3)
- Tosca (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1986 November 1 (Box 3)
- Tosca (New York City Opera, New York, NY), 1987 October 24 (Box 3)
- Tosca (The Washington Opera, Washington, DC), 1988 November 13 (Box 3)
- Tosca (San Francisco Opera, San Francisco, CA), 1992 September 15 (Box 3)
- Tosca (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1992 October 27 (Box 3)
- Tosca (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1993 October 23 (Box 3)
- Tosca (Lyric Opera of Chicago, Chicago, IL), 1993 November 8 (Box 3)
- Tosca (The Santa Fe Opera, Santa Fe, NM), 1994 July 6 (Box 3)
- Tosca (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1995 March 25 (Box 3)
- Tosca (Opera Theatre of St. Louis, St. Louis, MO), 1995 June 22 (Box 3)
- Tosca (L.A. Opera, Los Angeles, CA), 1996 November 20 (Box 3)
- Tosca (San Francisco Opera, San Francisco, CA), 1997 September 18 (Box 3)
- Tosca (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1998 October 15 (Box 3)
- Tosca (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1999 November 15 (Box 3)
- Tosca (The Washington Opera, Washington, DC), 2000 March 7 (Box 3)
- Tosca (Lyric Opera of Chicago, Chicago, IL), 2001 March 15 (Box 3)
- Tosca (San Francisco Opera, San Francisco, CA), 2001 November 11 (Box 3)
- Die tote Stadt (New York City Opera, New York, NY), 2001 April 24 (Box 3)
- La Trahison Orale (Spoleto Festival, Charleston, SC), 1994 May 27 (Box 3)
- Transformations (Opera Theatre of St. Louis, St. Louis, MO), 1997 June 20 (Box 3)
- La Traviata (Teatro alla Scala, Milan, Italy), 1964 December 20 (Box 3)
- La Traviata (Canadian Opera Company, Durham, NC), 1977 February 18 (Box 3)
- La Traviata (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1977 December 16 (Box 3)
- La Traviata (San Diego Opera, San Diego, CA), 1979 June 29 (Box 3)
- La Traviata (The Santa Fe Opera, Santa Fe, NM), 1980 August 6 (Box 3)
- La Traviata (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1981 April 10 (Box 3)
- La Traviata (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1981 September 26 (Box 3)
- La Traviata (Varsity Theater, Chapel Hill, NC), 1983 June 10 (Box 3)
- La Traviata (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1983 November 17 (Box 3)
- La Traviata (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1985 November 2 (Box 3)
- La Traviata (Lyric Opera of Chicago, Chicago, IL), 1985 December 1 (Box 3)
- La Traviata (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1987 November 28 (Box 3)
- La Traviata (Lyric Opera of Chicago, Chicago, IL), 1988 October 8 (Box 3)
- La Traviata (The Washington Opera, Washington, DC), 1988 November 12 (Box 3)
- La Traviata (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1989 October 28 (Box 3)
- La Traviata (The Santa Fe Opera, Santa Fe, NM), 1991 August 5 (Box 3)
- La Traviata (San Francisco Opera, San Francisco, CA), 1991 November 25 (Box 3)
- La Traviata (Lyric Opera of Chicago, Chicago, IL), 1993 October 4 (Box 3)
- La Traviata (Triangle Opera Theater, Durham, NC), 1994 June 1 (Box 3)
- La Traviata (San Francisco Opera, San Francisco, CA), 1995 September 23 (Box 3)
- La Traviata (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1996 October 12 (Box 3)
- La Traviata (The Washington Opera, Washington, DC), 1997 March 18 (Box 3)
- La Traviata (The Santa Fe Opera, Santa Fe, NM), 1997 July 5 (Box 3)
- La Traviata (Western Opera Theater, Chapel Hill, NC), 1998 November 12 (Box 3)
- La Traviata (Houston Grand Opera, Houston, TX), 1999 February 7 (Box 3)
- La Traviata (Lyric Opera of Chicago, Chicago, IL), 1999 February 22 (Box 3)
- La Traviata (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 2000 February 12 (Box 3)
- La Traviata (Opera Theatre of St. Louis, St. Louis, MO), 2000 June 24 (Box 3)
- La Traviata (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 2001 December 15 (Box 3)
- La Traviata (The Santa Fe Opera, Santa Fe, NM), 2002 July 20 (Box 3)
- Treemonisha (Opera Theatre of St. Louis, St. Louis, MO), 2000 June 24 (Box 3)
- Trial By Jury (The Charleston Opera Chorus, Charleston, SC), 1980 May 27 (Box 3)
- Tristan and Iseult (Spoleto Festival, Charleston, SC), 1990 May 21 (Box 3)
- Tristan und Isolde (Staatsoper, Vienna, Austria), 1980 June 20 (Box 3)
- Tristan und Isolde (Spoleto Festival, Charleston, SC), 1985 June 12 (Box 3)
- Tristan und Isolde (San Francisco Opera, San Francisco, CA), 1991 November 5 (Box 3)
- Tristan und Isolde (L.A. Opera, Los Angeles, CA), 1997 February 18 (Box 3)
- Tristan und Isolde (San Francisco Opera, San Francisco, CA), 1998 October 21 (Box 3)
- Tristan und Isolde (The Washington Opera, Washington, DC), 1999 February 27 (Box 3)
- Tristan und Isolde (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1999 December 11 (Box 3)
- Tristan und Isolde (Houston Grand Opera, Houston, TX), 2000 February 5 (Box 3)
- Tristan und Isolde (Lyric Opera of Chicago, Chicago, IL), 2000 March 4 (Box 3)
- Trouble in Tahiti (The Opera Company of NC, Raleigh, NC), 1999 January 15 (Box 3)
- Il Trovatore (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1978 January 27 (Box 3)
- Il Trovatore (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1982 January 28 (Box 3)
- Il Trovatore (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1982 December 13 (Box 3)
- Il Trovatore (The Washington Opera, Washington, DC), 1986 November 13 (Box 3)
- Il Trovatore (Lyric Opera of Chicago, Chicago, IL), 1987 October 16 (Box 3)
- Il Trovatore (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1987 December 5 (Box 3)
- Il Trovatore (Opera Columbus, Columbus, OH), 1990 April 28 (Box 3)
- Il Trovatore (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1993 February 27 (Box 3)
- Il Trovatore (Lyric Opera of Chicago, Chicago, IL), 1994 January 22 (Box 3)
- Il Trovatore (San Francisco Opera, San Francisco, CA), 1994 September 22 (Box 3)
- Il Trovatore (L.A. Opera, Los Angeles, CA), 1998 May 13 (Box 3)
- Il Trovatore (The Washington Opera, Washington, DC), 2000 November 13 (Box 3)
- Il Trovatore (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 2001 March 26 (Box 3)
- Les Troyens (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1983 September 26 (Box 3)
- The Tsar Has His Photograph Taken (The Santa Fe Opera, Santa Fe, NM), 1993 July 31 (Box 3)
- The Tsar's Bride (The Washington Opera, Washington, DC), 1986 November 16 (Box 3)
- The Tsar's Bride (The Washington Opera, Washington, DC), 1992 November 14 (Box 3)
- The Tsar's Bride (San Francisco Opera, San Francisco, CA), 2000 September 24 (Box 3)
- Turandot (San Francisco Opera, San Francisco, CA), 1964 December 19 (Box 3)
- Turandot (Teatro alla Scala, Milan, Italy), 1964 December 19 (Box 3)
- Turandot (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1987 April 4 (Box 3)
- Turandot (Opera Australia, Sydney Opera House, Sydney, Australia), 1992 January 11 (Box 3)
- Turandot (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1992 February 1 (Box 3)
- Turandot (The Washington Opera, Washington, DC), 1993 March 13 (Box 3)
- Turandot (San Francisco Opera, San Francisco, CA), 1993 October 26 (Box 3)
- Turandot (Opera Australia, Sydney Opera House, Sydney, Australia), 1995 January 7 (Box 3)
- Turandot (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1995 January 27 (Box 3)
- Turandot (Lyric Opera of Chicago, Chicago, IL), 1997 February 4 (Box 3)
- Turandot (New York City Opera, New York, NY), 1997 April 6 (Box 3)
- Turandot (San Diego Opera, San Diego, CA), 1997 May 7 (Box 3)
- Turandot (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1997 October 11 (Box 3)
- Turandot (San Francisco Opera, San Francisco, CA), 1998 September 22 (Box 3)
- Turandot (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 2000 November 3 (Box 3)
- Turandot (The Washington Opera, Washington, DC), 2001 March 21 (Box 3)
- Turandot (San Francisco Opera, San Francisco, CA), 2002 September 10 (Box 3)
- Turandot (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 2002 October 19 (Box 3)
- The Turk in Italy (New York City Opera, New York, NY), 1979 May 5 (Box 3)
- The Turk in Italy (Opera Theatre of St. Louis, St. Louis, MO), 1992 June 20 (Box 3)
- The Turn of the Screw (The Santa Fe Opera, Santa Fe, NM), 1983 August 12 (Box 3)
- The Turn of the Screw (Des Moines Metro Opera, Des Moines, IA), 1987 July 11 (Box 3)
- The Turn of the Screw (Seattle Opera, Seattle, WA), 1994 March 10 (Box 3)
- The Turn of the Screw (New York City Opera, New York, NY), 1996 October 3 (Box 3)
- The Turn of the Screw (New York City Opera, New York, NY), 2000 October 3 (Box 3)
- Un Ballo in Maschera (Stockholm Opera, Stockholm, Sweden), 1966 August 24 (Box 3)
- Un Ballo in Maschera (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1980 March 8 (Box 3)
- Un Ballo in Maschera (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1981 January 31 (Box 3)
- Un Ballo in Maschera (San Diego Opera, San Diego, CA), 1982 June 19 (Box 3)
- Un Ballo in Maschera (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1982 October 30 (Box 3)
- Un Ballo in Maschera (San Francisco Opera, San Francisco, CA), 1985 November 23 (Box 3)
- Un Ballo in Maschera (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1990 November 9 (Box 3)
- Un Ballo in Maschera (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1991 September 28 (Box 3)
- Un Ballo in Maschera (Lyric Opera of Chicago, Chicago, IL), 1992 December 7 (Box 3)
- Un Ballo in Maschera (Opera House, Washington, DC), 1994 March 6 (Box 3)
- Un Ballo in Maschera (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1995 December 9 (Box 3)
- Un Ballo in Maschera (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1997 March 7 (Box 3)
- Un Ballo in Maschera (San Francisco Opera, San Francisco, CA), 1999 September 23 (Box 3)
- Un Ballo in Maschera (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 2001 April 14 (Box 3)
- Un Ballo in Maschera (Opera House, Washington, DC), 2002 April 14 (Box 3)
- Un Giorno di Regno (The National Opera Company, Durham, NC), 1978 November 3 (Box 3)
- Un Giorno di Regno (San Diego Opera, San Diego, CA), 1981 June 20 (Box 3)
- Un Re in Ascolto (Lyric Opera of Chicago, Chicago, IL), 1996 November 12 (Box 3)
- Under the Double Moon (Opera Theatre of St. Louis, St. Louis, MO), 1989 June 23 (Box 3)
- The Unicorn, The Gorgon and The Manticore (Spoleto Festival, Charleston, SC), 2000 June 6 (Box 3)
- Vanessa (Opera Theatre of St. Louis, St. Louis, MO), 1988 June 12 (Box 3)
- Vanessa (The Washington Opera, Washington, DC), 1995 February 4 (Box 3)
- The Vanishing Bridegroom (Opera Theatre of St. Louis, St. Louis, MO), 1992 June 18 (Box 3)
- Venus and Adonis (The Santa Fe Opera, Santa Fe, NM), 2000 July 29 (Box 3)
- I Vespri Siciliani (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1982 March 27 (Box 3)
- I Vespri Siciliani (San Francisco Opera, San Francisco, CA), 1993 September 23 (Box 3)
- Il Viaggio a Reims (New York City Opera, New York, NY), 1999 September 29 (Box 3)
- La Vida Breve (Sydney Town Hall, Sydney, Australia), 1997 January 17 (Box 3)
- A View from the Bridge (Lyric Opera of Chicago, Chicago, IL), 1999 October 25 (Box 3)
- The Visit of the Old Lady (New York City Opera, New York, NY), 1997 April 8 (Box 3)
- A Visit to the Country (Ava Opera Theatre, Philadelphia, PA), 1997 April 29 (Box 3)
- Von Heute auf Morgen (The Santa Fe Opera, Santa Fe, NM), 1980 August 7 (Box 3)
- The Voyage (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1992 October 28 (Box 3)
- The Voyage (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1996 March 22 (Box 3)
- The Voyage of Edgar Allan Poe (Lyric Opera of Chicago, Chicago, IL), 1990 October 30 (Box 3)
- Die Walkure (Seattle Opera, Seattle, WA), 1982 August 2 (Box 3)
- Die Walkure (San Francisco Opera, San Francisco, CA), 1985 June 4 (Box 3)
- Die Walkure (Seattle Opera, Seattle, WA), 1986 August 11 (Box 3)
- Die Walkure (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1986 October 4 (Box 3)
- Die Walkure (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1987 October 31 (Box 3)
- Die Walkure (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1989 May 2 (Box 3)
- Die Walkure (Lyric Opera of Chicago, Chicago, IL), 1993 December 6 (Box 3)
- Die Walkure (San Francisco Opera, San Francisco, CA), 1995 November 15 (Box 3)
- Die Walkure (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1997 April 7 (Box 3)
- Die Walkure (Seattle Opera, Seattle, WA), 2001 August 22 (Box 3)
- War and Peace (Seattle Opera, Seattle, WA), 1990 July 29 (Box 3)
- War and Peace (San Francisco Opera, San Francisco, CA), 1991 September 26 (Box 3)
- War and Peace (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 2002 March 15 (Box 3)
- Werther (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1978 October 7 (Box 3)
- Werther (Lyric Opera of Chicago, Chicago, IL), 1978 November 10 (Box 3)
- Werther (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1985 March 10 (Box 3)
- Werther (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1988 April 16 (Box 3)
- Werther (Opera Theatre of St. Louis, St. Louis, MO), 1989 June 24 (Box 3)
- Werther (The Washington Opera, Washington, DC), 1990 January 28 (Box 3)
- Werther (The Washington Opera, Washington, DC), 1996 January 29 (Box 3)
- Wiener Blut (The Washington Opera, Washington, DC), 1987 February 7 (Box 3)
- The Woman at Otowl Crossing (Opera Theatre of St. Louis, St. Louis, MO), 1995 June 21 (Box 3)
- Wonderful Town (New York City Opera, New York, NY), 1994 November 9 (Box 3)
- The Woodlanders (Opera Theatre of St. Louis, St. Louis, MO), 1985 June 21 (Box 3)
- Wozzeck (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1980 March 8 (Box 3)
- Wozzeck (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1985 February 8 (Box 3)
- Wozzeck (Lyric Opera of Chicago, Chicago, IL), 1994 January 24 (Box 3)
- Wozzeck (Spoleto Festival, Charleston, SC), 1997 May 23 (Box 3)
- Wozzeck (Metropolitan Opera, New York, NY), 1999 April 17 (Box 3)
- Wozzeck (San Francisco Opera, San Francisco, CA), 1999 November 5 (Box 3)
- Wozzeck (The Santa Fe Opera, Santa Fe, NM), 2001 July 28 (Box 3)
- X (The Life and Times of Malcolm X) (New York City Opera, New York, NY), 1986 October 5 (Box 3)
- Xerxes (The Santa Fe Opera, Santa Fe, NM), 1993 July 17 (Box 3)
- Xerxes (The Santa Fe Opera, Santa Fe, NM), 1993 August 11 (Box 3)
- Xerxes (Lyric Opera of Chicago, Chicago, IL), 1995 October 9 (Box 3)
- Xerxes (New York City Opera, New York, NY), 1997 November 3 (Box 3)